vaporzone.com 2014-12-13

# VaporFi | Privacy Policy

Effective September 1, 2013

#### Website Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

Click here for our Terms of Use

VaporFi electronic cigarette products are intended for use exclusively by adult smokers and in no way ever intended for use by pregnant women or those who have nicotine sensitivities. Nicotine, as it is commonly known, is a highly addictive substance and may possess unknown health dangers. VaporFi electronic cigarettes are not intended for use as smoking cessation devices; they are merely alternatives for those who wish to use smoke-free, tobacco-free devices that provide utmost pleasure.

#### SURGEON GENERAL'S WARNING: 

Smoking is Known to Cause Lung Cancer, Heart Disease, Emphysema, and May Complicate Pregnancy.

#### Warning: 

CONTAINS LIQUID NICOTINE - KEEP OUT OF REACH OF CHILDREN.

Nicotine liquid is harmful when it comes in direct contact with the skin. Should this occur, the area of skin should be washed immediately upon contact with soap and water. Should the nicotine liquid get swallowed or placed in the mouth at all, immediately seek medical attention due to the risk of nicotine poisoning. Stay smart; stay safe!

#### Our Privacy Policy

Your privacy is not something we take lightly, as we are committed to building solid business relationships, which require earning and maintaining trust. We understand the importance of a strict privacy policy when it comes to sensitive, personal information being transmitted on the internet, and due to this we take it very seriously.

We wish to communicate what forms of information we collect from you, how this information can be used and protected, and you are able to control its use.

This statement is designed to disclose the privacy practices of Cavo Partners, Inc. d/b/a VaporFi.* By using this website, you are agreeing to be bound by this Privacy Policy, without qualification or limitation.

The information contained within this Privacy Policy strictly applies to the collection and use of information by VaporFi on this website. It does not apply to any of the information you send to us by other means. Any alterations or modifications to this Privacy Policy will be communicated here on this page, so it is important to check back on occasion.

#### Who is permitted to use this website. 

Adults only. This website, in no way whatsoever, has been intended, designed, or manipulated to attract the attention of users under the age of 18/21, depending on the state laws of the individual regarding the legal smoking age. We do not collect data which may be considered personally identifiable from any person known to be below the age of 18/ 21. We state clearly that this site is not intended for those under the legal smoking age, and furthermore, we instruct those individuals to not send us information.

The information contained on this site is restricted to users in the United States. Regarding users in other countries, it is highly advisable not to disclose your personal information on this website. The data, which you transmit, is sent to a server in the State of Florida, subject to the laws of the United States as well as the laws of the State of Florida. By sending personal information and data to this website, you are agreeing to be bound by the United States and the laws of the State of Florida.

#### Information collected from you. 

The information we collect from you varies, depending on the ways you use our website, and not all browsing results in the collection of date, personal or otherwise. It is highly possible you may browse our site without submitting any personal information however there are instances where submitting information, such as your name, address, email address, etc is required.

Besides the information you choose to submit, our systems are programmed to collect certain types of data on an anonymous level. This is done to give us insight on how our site is being used, as well as to help us understand how we may improve it in the future. This typically entails automatically gathering data such as any of the content you view on our website.

#### How your information is used. 

On our website, we utilize “cookies.” What these are is small files, which we send to and store on your computer so that we are able to recognize it as a unique machine on your next visit. These cookies allow us to know you are a prior customer and they allow us to personalize the experience for you, providing useful information, advertisements, and messages that may be of interest to you. It should also be known that outside companies offering their products or services through our website may be using their own cookies.

When you provide personal information, it is used to customize your online experience on our website. For instance, your email address is a unique identifier and is kept in our records. When used in conjunction with a password, it is excellent towards the prevention of unauthorized access to any of the information you willingly store on our site. Information you send to use, such as age, occupation, ZIP code, or other data may be used to offer personalized content, beneficial advertisements, products, and additional services that are most likely going to appeal to you based on the information given.

We use personal information to respond directly to requests you may make of us, as well as reference this information should we feel the need to better understand your needs and how we may be able to improve our services, products, and website. We may also be inclined to use this personal information to contact you and/ or provide information we deem may be useful to you such as promotions. There is a possibility that we may share this information with additional companies whose products and services may be of interest to you. There is also a possibility we may enhance or merge this information with data we obtain from third parties for these same intended purposes. Unless specified that you wish not to receive communications from us, we may also send you promotional and/or administrative communications via the email address you have provided. Terminating these communications typically takes a period of 48 hours to take hold from the time you give us notice.

Information such as your computer’s IP address, the browser you use, and a navigation record are types of the information our system gathers, and it is used for purposes of improving our products, services, and website, enhancing convenience, and providing useful content to our audience. The collection of data is also done to further our goal of providing top service, as well as useful content, beneficial advertisements, and products that are going to appeal to you. In this manner, we may link information we have collected from you through a variety of means including automatically as well as through the use of cookies and personal information, and the information gathered via VaporFi’s Customer Care and Home Delivery Program.

#### Your Options Regarding the Usage of Your Personal Information. 

*You always hold the option to not provide personal information, even if it is necessary to take part in VaporFi offers or website features.

*You have the option to alter, add to, or update certain information you send to us. Let it be known however, when information is updated we usually retain a copy of the original version in our records.

*If you wish not to receive email communications or other mail from us, of if you want to check your personal information, please feel free to contact us via email at service@vaporfi.com

#### Access to Your Personal Information. 

VaporFi may use your personal information to reply to you as well as to send information to you. In no way does VaporFi intend to disclose personal information to third parties except those explicitly stated in this Privacy Policy. It should be known that VaporFi will provide aggregated information, which we receive from you, to third parties. VaporFi takes commercially accepted precautions in efforts of preventing this information from including personal information.

In the event that VaporFi, or our assets are sold, transferred, or used as security, the personal information we have collected through our website may become transferred to third parties in connection with that transaction. VaporFi may also give access to, or provide personal information to any of our business affiliates and/ or business partners.

In the event that VaporFi is requested by law enforcement officials and/or judicial authorities to provide personal information on individuals who have used our system, VaporFi may, without your consent, provide any of this information. In matters that involve claims of public or personal safety or litigation where this data is considered pertinent, VaporFi may use or disclose your personal information without your consent or court process.

#### Will Your Personal Information Be Secure? 

VaporFi recognizes and understands your concerns on the subject of safety and security regarding your personal information. We are 100% committed to using reasonable technology to protect your information as well as the overall security of our website. With that said, it should be noted that even with such advanced technology, no website is 100% secure. We take reasonable precautions and measures, which we firmly believe are appropriate for protecting your information from alteration, abuse, misuse, loss, and/ or destruction. We also request that any third parties we are affiliated with, whom we may transfer your information to take the same or comparable steps to protect your information and security.

#### VaporFi Privacy Policy and Outside Links. 

VaporFi Privacy Policy applies only to this website, however our website does contain links to outside sites that are beyond our control. Be advised that these sites have the potential to collect personal information about you, and they will operate according to their own privacy practices that may differ from our own Privacy Policy. It is advised that you consult any such websites’ privacy policies, as once you are no longer on VaporFi’s website, any of the information you submit is beyond our control.

#### Questions Regarding This Privacy Policy. 

Should you have any questions, concerns, or comments regarding our privacy practices, please do not hesitate to e-mail us at service@VaporFi.com

This policy was last updated on September 1, 2013
